A day when boys give girls the best hospitality
Emo, emo, emo, emo, emo, emo, emo.
Emo. Emo.
Our female members love broccoli.
I'm not sure what to put in it.
I love one heart here
Fukazawa The food store is out!
Sakuma, ugh!
Sakuma, wait!
Abe, what's this?
Sakuma, why did I say salad cheese?
Fukazawa, he wants to put a salad in it.
Sakuma, that's right.
Tomato sauce, rice omelet, and...
Fukazawa, there's omu-rice with tomato sauce.
Fukazawa There's an omelet with tomato sauce.
Fukazawa I wanted to make that.
Fukazawa I see.
Fukazawa, why don't we put you in charge? Who's in charge?
Abe, we talked about buying hamburgers.
Abe, I want to make hamburgers.
Abe Noodles.
Fukazawa, I'm in charge of omelette rice.
Abe I'm in charge of omelette rice.
Abe I'd like you to be in charge of omelette rice.
Fukazawa I see.
Fukazawa Then I'll be in charge.
Abe, I'd like you to help me with the hamburger.
Abe, you make them so fluffy.
Abe, I'm going to make this. Abe I'm going to make this.
Fukazawa Leave it to me.
Abe, please make the first move.
Abe, I just bought ingredients for hamburgers and omelettes.
Abe, I bought ingredients for an omu-rice.
We don't have much time.
Fukazawa That's right.
Abe, let's make it right away.
Abe, you're going to get hit in the eye.
Fukazawa, will it hurt your eyes?
Fukazawa, I'm cutting onions later.
Fukazawa, did someone get hit in the eye?
Fukazawa I'm not very good at cutting.
Fukazawa, ask him first.
Fukazawa, did you know they specialize in eggs?
Abe, I don't know.
Fukazawa You have to put air in them.
Fukazawa By doing that...
Fukazawa Look at this beautiful color.
The color.
Fukazawa You didn't think we could cook, did you?
Fukazawa, hi
Fukazawa, I'm a popular guy.
Abe, so far we haven't even made a pretty face.
Fukazawa I'm just beating eggs.
Abe, you can wear glasses.
Fukazawa, you can wear glasses
Fukazawa Oh! Haruma Sasahara's glasses work!
Abe, wait, Koya's late.
Abe, Koya's a little late. He's getting ready for something. Abe: Koya, I'm preparing a lot of things.
Fukazawa Oh, really?
Abe, I'm working on it.
Fukazawa, sooner or later...
Fukazawa, maybe we'll get married...
Sakuma, if we were a couple... a married couple...
Sakuma Wouldn't that be a wonderful couple?
Abe, it's true, I don't feel like I'm working.
Abe It's like we're chasing a dream.
Abe, Atz.
Fukazawa Atz is so cool.
Abe, maybe I'll just have one onion.
Abe, you don't want cream?
Fukazawa, of course you do.
Sakuma Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!
Fukazawa, you put too much!
Fukazawa Oh, no!
Sakuma Fighting with myself
Sakuma I'll try something I didn't do today
Fukazawa This time, I thought it would be lonely with only onions...
Fukazawa, I'd like to add my rivalry
I'm going to put in some onions
Everyone hahaha hahaha
All together Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
Uhh!
Wait!
Aah!
Next!
Embarrassing.Embarrassing.
I don't have any.
I'm cooking.
I just...
I'm thinking I'd like to do without one move.
I'll do without.
One of them recently started cooking.
I've heard that one of them has started cooking recently.
One of them recently...
Sha sha sha sha sha
Eiko.
Eiko?
Am I right now?
Yes, sir.
Let's get this over here, and I'll go fry some onions.
I'll go fry some onions.
Let's have Kouki make a fancy salad.
Jesse, I'll make it.
Okay.
You do it with your own taste.
Yo!
Well, it's something like that, isn't it?
I'm really honored that Eikou-chan came
Really?
It's so big!
A little too big
How's Egamuyu?
Oh, no!
It's nice.
Oh, my God.Oh, man.
Okay, okay, okay.
Here we go.
Yeah!
I'm going to make a big salad.
A big salad.
Hot, hot, hot!
Jiro, Joki, Joki! It's so good!
Joki Joki, it's so good!
Joki, Joki, Joki. Looks so good.
Joki, wow!
Joki, wow, it's good!
Wow, it's good!
It's very good.
Wow, it's good, it's good, it's good
No, the ocean is beautiful.
I'll make the dressing.
I'll do whatever you want.
First, a drizzle of olive oil.
What?
And a dash of capsicum.
By volume? I'm not measuring, I'm...
Cabos?
Put the kabosu.
Cute.
And a little lemon juice.
Add salt.
That's good.
I don't need salt.
Do I just add pepper if I put it in?Do I just put the pepper in?
No, I don't.
Pepper?
What do you put them in?
Apples are best as they are.
Yes, seriously, you've got a delicious dressing.
Oh, that's good.
Hey, voice, I want you to hold that in front of the door.
Okay. - Okay.
Inside, I'll waitress.
You got it.
I'm going to greet the master now.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Wait.
What?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Huh?
What is it?
Wait!
Um, I'm Aikon, the waitress.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Yeah!
Why, why, why, why!
What?
Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my God!
Amazing!That's great!
Wait, no!
Cute!
Treat, treat!
Oh, look at that.
Oh, thank you.
Cute!
Adorable!
Drinkable type
White drinkable type
White drinkable
I mean, it smells so good.
Hey!
What?
Oh, my God!
Oh, man! Oh, my God!
I made that salad!
It's really half-cooked! The eggs!
What? Yes! That was a great idea!
Oh, man! That was awesome!
Oh my God, I can't stop smiling!
It's so funny! The quality never goes down!Interesting! High quality image never goes down!
Oh my god! It's so funny!
I'm so happy! This would have been a normal project!
I'm sure! Very nice!
We have omelette rice, but how much rice do you want?
What do you want?
A normal serving! A normal serving!
One serving!
I bought a normal serving!
Bye bye!
I'm really impressed to see a side of boys I've never seen before.
It's like they can cook. I'm looking forward to it. I can't wait to see the finished product.
It looks delicious.
Last but not least, Amu-kun's specialty, eggs.
I can't wait to see the ketchup hearts on this.
Yay! I've been waiting for this!
I hope it tastes good. I hope it tastes good. Moe moe moe kyun!
So cute!
Now, Ayume from Kyushu is going to make omu-rice.
Well, I heard that there will be a visit.
I want to see, I want to see!
Let me see it in my hands.
I want to see!
Ah! They have hamburgers!
Yum! Yum!
Wait!
What? Huh? Huh?
Give it back to me at the far end.
Goo!
Goo! Goo!
Oh, it broke in two.
But isn't it really fluffy?
It's so good!
It sure is good.
Both are good.
It looks so delicious!
I was nervous. I was so nervous.
Hey, wait, that's amazing!
Oh, no, it's broken.
That's enough.
I'll do my best!
The best place is Halloween.
Hey, I'll try next time.
What? That's enough, isn't it?
You're good too, right?
That's good!
What? Is it good?
Amazing!
I'll do it again.
Oh! Oh!
Yummy, yummy, yummy!
Yummy!
Whoo!
Yum!
Looks so good!
And they're wearing stylish éclat, so you'll have to buy the store!
Looks delicious!
Looks fun!
Next! Next!
Wow!
Thank you!
Looks delicious!
Oh, my gosh!
Looks so good!
Wait, oh my God!
Oh, my God!
Okay, I'm in charge of the hamburgers first.
Oh!
Salad, sir!
I made ice cream.
Oh!
I made omelet eggs!
Oh, we made salad!
Yes!
She made the dressing.
Thank you very much.
Who made the cucumber and egg?
I did. I did.
Oh, my God!
That's amazing!
We all worked so hard from the shopping trip!
Oh!
The two of you did the decorations in the back.
Koya and Amu did one.
Aah!
[ED][ED.
Tomatoes OK please
Tomato OK.
Thank you.
It's big.
A little more.
I'm supposed to eat alone.
I'm sure it will be divided into thirds.
It's cute that you said it should be divided into thirds.
Bon appétit!
Is it good?
Delicious!
What kind of dressing is this?
It's capsicum, lemon juice, Oz, olive oil, salt and pepper.
Looks delicious!
It's something quite refreshing and very easy to eat and delicious!
Thank you.
Yay!
You look so shy!
I'm going to try the tomatoes!
It's so good!
What did you eat?
Tomatoes.
It's so good!
We don't like raw cheese.
I love it.
I like it best.
Thank you. - Oh, my God.
This is so good.
I love...I was.
Kudo did it.
I would like to start with boiled eggs
half-boiled
Delicious!
Put broccoli dressing on it.
Bon appétit!
Mmm.
So soft!
So good!
It's wonderful.
Bon appétit!
It's so delicious!
It's so good!
What? It's so good!
It's so delicious!
It's really delicious just because it was made by a member.
Thank you very much.
I think it means we can have fun when girls cook.
No, no, no, no, this is why it's good.
It's delicious.
It's better than the girls.
Wow! The eggs are fluffy and tender and delicious!
It's so delicious!
Bon appétit!
Delicious! Delicious!
Mmm!
It's so good!
It's good, right? It's so good!
You all should try it!
Thank you very much.
It's so good!
I'll eat it with you, then.
Mmm, it's good.
It's so good.
The sauce and eggs are so good.
Thank you very much.
Wait.
Mom is so bad at mixing.
A side dish that needs to be mixed.
A side dish that you don't mix.
It's so good.
Oh, man!
Bon appétit!
Yum!
It's so good!
Wow.
You're good.
You're good at it sometimes.
Yeah, it's good.
It's good.
It's not good.Oh man.
I didn't expect such delicious food from those boys!
I want to stick it in here.
Oh, nice nice nice
Here it comes, here it comes!
Here's dessert!
Wow!
Looks so delicious!
Thank you.
You're the winner.
Best game.
This is the best game I've ever played.
Bon appétit.
Mmm.
Delicious!
The best
Good luck, good luck, good luck
Let's get inside this baby together.
First of all, all the boys
For all of us
They did a lot of thinking for us
and cooking for us.
Thank you very, very much.
Not only for the food, but also for the hearts of the boys.
It makes me very happy.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
It was so genuinely delicious.
I enjoyed it very much.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
The delicious food just keeps coming.
I'm so happy!
I'm so happy.
I don't know if this is a good idea.
I'd like to give the MVP to everyone today.
I'd like to give you the MVP today.
Thank you very much.
I also got 100 points.
I'm sure there was a lot of love in there already, so...
I can't.
Come on, put some heart into it.
Of course it was.
But thank you for the 100.
So, how was dinner? Did you enjoy it?
We're fine.
Thank you very much.
But there's more.
Here's where the fun begins.
What is it?
Let's play a wargame first.
Yes, we had fun playing wargames.
That was the game time of the hospitality project!
Yay!
I have something important to tell you.
What?
At the end, I wrote a letter to everyone.
Yay!
Okay, I'll go. Then I'll go.
Okay, I'll go.
Let's go to One Man Heart.
Everyone, it's already time for our FIX One Man Live at Skyzer Limit Zep Shinjuku,
We are now practicing the basics and developing our skills for that stage.
We are now practicing the basics and improving our skills for that stage.
The basic training is hard and we haven't even started the rehearsal period for the One Man Live yet,
I think time is still running out.
I think that time is still running out.
But summer is already over and November will soon come,
I had various live concerts with other bands,
I had a lot of one man live concerts, and then I went into December right away,
Then we will already start rehearsals for the One Man Live.
And then we have to start rehearsals for the One Man Live.
Then I think about the show on January 8,
I think that there are really only a few days left.
What I would like to do here is to raise everyone's spirits.
I would like to close this event with everyone's excitement and one arm in the air.
I hope that we can close this time with a feeling of excitement.
It may be a little early and difficult for everyone to think about it yet, but
I want to take it up a notch here.
Let's all get our feelings together and breathe in unison
Toward working hard toward a single goal
I hope that the stage of Sky the Limit on October 8 will be even better.
I think we will be able to perform even better.
I think we can perform even better.
I trust you all
I'd like to send you all as my life partner
I want to send them to the next
I'm going to send them to the force one-man live I'll be at the Force one-man live show.
I said.
This is what I really think
I'm so happy to see you all that even now I'm thankful to be a part of this group.
It makes me want to be with you all the time.
I can say that this love one is my youth.
I've been able to enjoy my days so much that I could say this Love One is my youth.
I am truly fulfilled.
It is the members of Love One who have made me feel that way.
and all the fans who support us on a daily basis.
and the staff.
I think it is the family of One Love One Heart
I think that's why I can be thankful.
So when I think about why I can be thankful...
I think that this place is something we take for granted.
I don't know what's really in store for us in the future.
But I want to be with you all.
I thought that if I thought about what I should do, the answer would come to me immediately.
I think that we should bury our despair and aim for a higher stage together.
I think...
I really think there's only one thing to do.
I still want to spend time with everyone in this one and only space called Love One
I want to keep running toward my dream.
The Love One family will be united as one
Let's all run together toward Tokyo Dome, the group's dream.
That's what the letter said.
This one's pretty cool.
That's what I like about it!
He rewrote it so well!
That's great!Wow!
Oh, beautiful!
Haruko, you're beautiful!
Haruko is beautiful!
The thing that resonated the most with me was
That I want to be with this group forever.
It really touched my heart.
I really want to be a member of this group
I really want to make my various dreams come true with this group.
I'm really happy to know that we share the same feelings.
I am very happy to know that we share the same feelings.
As the oldest dancer in the group, I am very proud of you, Harumae.
I was very, very touched by your words.
Thank you very much!
How was our hospitality?
Funny!
It's a stylish place!
Like I said before, we raised it up on the middle level.
Let us remain on one stage
Let's run forward!
That's it!
That's all! This was a hospitality project!
Thank you very much!